

Husni Mubarak Ailatat Fullstack Developer

How to reach me:

Cell:

082134510421

Email:

husniailatat@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/husni-mubarak-ailatat-7186a2114/

Portfolio:

https://husnimubaraq.github.io/portfolio/

Address:

Bangunjiwo, Kasihan, Bantul, Yogyakarta

Github:

https://github.com/husnimubaraq/

Personal Profile

I am a Frontend Developer with more than 5 years experience. Have the ability and experience in designing, developing, and testing websites and mobile apps with the latest technology. Have experience backend development using the tech stack Laravel, Node JS, ASP.Net Core.

Education

Universitas PGRI Yogyakarta

S1 Teknik Informatika

My Skills

- Javascript
- Typescript
- React / Next JS
- React Native
- Node JS / Express
- PHP
- Laravel
- Codeginiter
- ASP.Net Core

Work Experience

Fullstack Developer

Gramedusa march 2022 to present

- Building and developing websites and mobile apps
- Optimizing performance apps
- Optimizing backend code and infrastructure for speed and efficiency.

Frontend Engineer

Synergize Tech April 2023 to March 2024

- Building and developing web apps
- Optimizing performance web apps
- Collaborate with UI/UX on feature design and implementation

Frontend Developer

PT Grahatour March 2020 to February 2022

- Building and developing websites and mobile apps
- Optimizing performance apps
- Collaborate with UI/UX on feature design and implementation

Frontend Developer

PT Ramcou Buana Informatika July 2018 to December 2019

- Modify an existing website and mobile to upgrade the interface tested and refined software prior to rollout
- Building and developing android apps
- Provide time estimates to the tech lead or project manager and help identify tasks for developing the project plan as needed